That was pretty close, Shido. Are you okay?
Mana? I...
Right. This is probably a little shocking, huh?
Excuse me, but we were in the middle of a lovely date, and I find it terribly rude of you to interrupt us like this.
Give me just a minute, big brother. This won't take very long.
Go to me!
Stop it! Don't kill her!
I knew it. You really are good, Shido.
Mana? Why?
How can you stand there like nothing happened? You just killed a person!
I just killed a spirit.
Besides, I do this all the time.
It is something all things are given. It cannot be bought, and it cannot be sold.
People often waste it, hold it dear, and chase after it.
If only we knew what it was.
Smoking against hope, why is it not the same?
I see what we have value, not with the same house.
Let's go, seriously.
Thank you.
Damn it!
Lana, why?
I don't know.
Why?
The plan's been aborted.
We'll pick you up for fractions.
Shido, can you hear me?
Shido!
What happened?
We've been looking for you.
Spill it.
What's going on?
Oh no, you've been hurt.
I'm so sorry.
Did I make it worse?
No.
Sorry.
Shido?
Shido!
Hey.
Is your arm feeling any better?
Yeah.
Good.
We can go then.
Wait, go where exactly?
We're continuing our date, silly.
Can I have some bread, please?
Court dogs!
See, pork buns!
Here.
Thanks.
That was sweet.
Come on, let's go!
Hold on!
Tolka, I don't have much money on me.
Don't worry about money.
Reina let me borrow her Magic Bythings card.
You mean credit card?
She also told me about you.
And Kurumi and Mana.
I see.
Then, you know I have to stop Kurumi from killing more people.
Yeah.
I'm just...
I'm not sure how I should go about it with her.
I mean, Kurumi's a spirit, but she's different from you or Yoshino.
Now, that isn't true at all, and you know it.
Kurumi and I are the same.
We are.
Remember that I had you here for me.
You saved me.
I didn't even know I needed you, but I did.
Then you asked me out on a date.
Like today, and showed me how amazing and beautiful this world really is.
If it weren't for you, Shido, I most likely would have ended up just like Kurumi.
There's only one difference between the two of us.
And that...
It's having someone close who's reaching out his hand.
Toka, thank you.
You've helped me realize what's important.
Yeah?
Does that mean you aren't scared?
No, not quite.
Don't worry.
I'll be here to protect you.
Thanks.
That makes me feel better.
I know, right?
Shido, can we stay like this for a while longer?
Sure.
Well, good morning, Shido.
How are you today?
I'm fine.
You are so dead, dude.
How dare you show your face around here?
That is, I don't know, lame.
Hold it.
Please, leave Shido alone.
Let's just go this way.
This is so lame.
I have to admit I'm a little surprised.
I thought for sure you wouldn't want to come to school today.
You know, after all that crazy drama.
Kurumi?
That's me.
So you know, I've made the decision that I need to save you.
Well, that's kind of a strange thing to say.
I will not let you kill anyone else.
I will also not let Mana kill you.
How very big of you.
Little Shido, I've made the decision I need to test you and see if you're really telling me the truth.
Ratadisker, huh?
I can't believe you and my big brother are part of that twisted organization.
I'm surprised you found that out.
Now what do you want?
It's about Shido.
You're negligent at best.
How could you send him unarmed to go meet with dangerous spirits?
You're a failure as a little sister.
So I'm going to take over that role from now on.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
And let a corrupt company like Deus Ex Machina get their hands on him?
I don't think so, Mana.
How did you know?
You should stop underestimating me.
I know that except for Ratadisker, your little group supplies all the military forces around the world with realizers.
And you, you're one of their employees who was sent to the AST.
Here he goes.
Kurumi has not been seen leaving the school as of yet.
Still though, our real problem is whether or not she'll listen to what we have to say.
Hey, where's Kotari?
Something just came up.
She'll be back soon, but this time I'll have to be your navigator.
Okay, got it.
Let's do this.
What happened?
Reina!
We're analyzing right now.
I'm not going to stand here and listen to you call us corrupt.
You know nothing about D.E.M.
That place gave me a reason to live after I lost my memory.
I can't thank them enough for their help.
Really? Even after what they did to you?
What are you talking about?
I've discovered something terrible from Manatakamiya's cup.
What they've done is wrong.
Her body has been implanted with far too much magical power.
Sadly, she's not likely to live more than ten years.
You don't know?
They haven't told you?
It's Kotari. What's up?
Commander, there's an intense spirit wave reaction at Shido's high school.
It's coming from Kurumi Tokusaki.
Understood.
It's a wide area barrier.
The kind of barrier meant to debilitate everyone within its range.
She did this, but why?
Hey, Shido.
Toka!
Are you all right?
Well, my body feels heavy for some reason.
Why am I the only one who's not affected?
Since you've sealed the powers of both Toka and Yoshino,
it's like you've received their divine protection.
Given these conditions, you're the only one who can move normally.
Shido darling, can you hear me?
If you need anything at all, feel free to join me on the roof.
Something tells me you might want to get here as soon as possible, though.
Listen to me.
Stay right here, okay?
And don't worry.
I'm going to save her.
Be careful, Shido.
Identifying A.S.T. Origami Tobeichi.
One basic realizer.
Activate at once.
Ah!
Welcome, Shido.
I'm glad you were so eager to come see me.
I'm showing you're using the emergency uniform.
What's going on?
Dangerous situation.
I need support.
Hello, Origami.
You seem like you're in a rush.
Where might you be off to?
I'm here to protect Shido from you.
No, that doesn't work for me.
Terribly sorry, but you'll have to stay right here.
Oh, Shido.
Don't go.
It's not safe to go up there alone.
Shido.
Come on.
Get up.
Move!
There you go, Toka.
I can do it.
Hey!
Who did that?
Kurumi?
Good morning, Toka.
Going anywhere?
Kurumi, what is all of this about?
Isn't it pretty?
My time eating castle?
This barrier sucks up the time from anyone who steps on my shadow.
The time?
Your eyes are clocked.
That's right.
What's your life?
Oh, Toka?
I can do it.
Hey!
Who did that?
Kurumi?
Kurumi, what is all of this about?
Isn't it pretty?
My time eating castle?
This barrier sucks up the time from anyone who steps on my shadow.
The time?
Your eyes are clocked.
That's right.
What you're looking at is my time.
Lovely thing.
I suppose you could call it my lifespan.
My angel has such a wonderful power.
But unfortunately, it does have that nasty habit of eating up my time whenever I use it.
So I have to replenish it with other people's time every once in a while.
What?
Other people's time?
Everyone is my pitiful, adorable prey.
But you...
You're special, Shido, and you don't even realize it.
Guess what?
You're the reason I'm here.
I came all this way just so I could become one with you in person and see the look on your face when I eat you.
Okay, fine, I'm the one you want.
So don't hurt everyone else!
I'll think about that option, but first I want you to take back what you said this morning.
Obviously you're not going to save me now, are you?
Come on, Shido.
Don't you think I'm downright awful to cause all this pain for such a silly reason?
You can say it.
You hate me and it's clear to you that I'm not someone who deserves mercy.
I will eat you, but first I'm giving you the chance to take your words back.
Do that, darling, and I'll reward you by taking down this barrier so those people won't die.
So what will it be, Shido?
Better make your decision quickly, or there will be nothing left for you to save.
Take down the barrier, Kurumi.
Do it.
But I will not give up on you.
Why are you so stubborn?
Your choices confuse me.
You know what that sound means, so what could I possibly be doing?
It's the spatial quake alarm.
A quake? She can, can she?
She's causing a spatial quake on purpose. We didn't know any spirit could do that.
What is my little Shido going to do if a spatial quake occurs now?
What do you imagine will happen to all those unconscious students?
Shin, Kurumi's emotional condition has started changing.
It seems almost as if she's frightened of you.
That's it.
Listen, you've been saying you came here just so you could eat me, right?
If that's true, stop the quake.
If you don't stop it,
I'll jump off this roof and kill myself.
You're making yourself a hostage?
Nice threat, but something tells me you're not going to follow through with it.
Watch me.
Are you kidding me?
Damn it. That was incredibly stupid.
I'm not as stupid as you think, because now I know I have worth to you as a hostage.
If you could go ahead and stop the spatial quake, that'd be great.
Oh, and take down the barrier while you're at it.
If you refuse, I swear I'll kill myself.
This is ridiculous.
Oh, there is one more thing.
How much more can there be?
I want you to allow yourself to have another chance.
Are we back to this?
Trust me, I'm more trouble than I'm worth.
That isn't true, even for you.
Listen to me.
You can change and be happy if you want, and I know you do.
I know it.
If that wasn't an option, you wouldn't have had so much fun on our date.
You're wrong. It's too late.
It's too late.
It's not too late.
I can help you!
Yes, you'll have to live with what you've done for the rest of your life.
But still, Kurumi, it doesn't matter how terrible you've been.
Nothing will ever give me a reason.
I can help you.
I don't know what you're trying to do to do.
I can help you!
Trust me.
I'm more trouble than I'm worth.
That isn't true, even for you.
Listen to me.
You can change and be happy if you want, and I know you do.
I know it.
If that wasn't an option, you wouldn't have had so much fun on our date.
You're wrong.
It's too late.
It's not too late.
Nothing will ever give me a reason not to save you.
What? I... I don't know.
Why are you so kind?
Am I worth it?
Can I...
It doesn't really work for us to have you fall for his pretty words, you know.
Thank you so much, Shido.
Well, that's that.
Why don't you go take a rest now?
Goodness me.
What? Kurumi? But how?
It seems the me I chose for this endeavor might have been a little too young.
Now, why don't we put a stop to this tediousness already?
Lana!
Hi. Are you ever not in trouble, big brother?
Right on time, like usual.
You've always had the strange ability to cut my spirit armor so easily.
This time, though...
Things have changed, so you might as well accept that I won't die and you won't live.
Hear me, Zavkiel! Come to me now!
Oh!
Day leto.
Your talent for healing is impressive.
your talent for healing is impressive i'm not healing in the least i'm simply turning back
the clock come fight let the fun begin sure bring it on i'll just kill you like i normally do
you still don't get it do you try as much as you like but there's no way you'll
ever be able to get rid of me completely we'll see about that get ready to die
olive
lana no
kurumi she's alive
please don't come any closer you're here oh how sweet looks like everyone made it kurumi
you're gonna pay for what you're doing here you can't run from us wow i'm positively terrified
to attack poor little kurumi with so many people all at once lucky for me though i'm playing for keeps
today
what the hell is all this this is my past my dear shito my history they're beautiful aren't they
now do you understand why i can never fully be killed where did they all come from time now we
need to finish this after you're gone i can be free there you go you should really stop getting
your hopes up for me shito i've taken some precautions to make sure you can't seduce me again no you can't
prepare to be surrounded by so much death the last thing you'll want to save is me please no
what is the meaning of this you mean you didn't know surprise surprise spatial
quakes can be neutralized if they run into a tremor of equal force at the onset
it's her what sis don't let me forget to give this back to you shito
burn kamai
bro what do you say are you about ready to begin our date
but
it's
man
you
Thank you.